{
    "subject": "resource/David_Burtka",
    "predicate": "property/yearsActive",
    "object": "Actor",
    "human_readable": "David Burtka was an Actor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9519935250282288,
            "question": "Was David Burtka known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7808328866958618,
            "question": "What was David Burtka's primary role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7742004990577698,
            "question": "What profession did David Burtka have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7189946174621582,
            "question": "What is David Burtka's known occupation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6555153131484985,
            "question": "How was David Burtka recognized in his profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6133386492729187,
            "question": "Was David Burtka involved in the performing arts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5931371450424194,
            "question": "What type of work was David Burtka involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5909287929534912,
            "question": "What is David Burtka best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5744284987449646,
            "question": "In what field did David Burtka make a career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4763529598712921,
            "question": "What did David Burtka do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Burtka was an Actor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1917_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what field did David Burtka make a career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1917_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is David Burtka best known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1917_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work was David Burtka involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1917_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1917_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1917_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1917_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1917_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1917_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1917_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1917_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1917_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1917_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1917_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"David Burtka was an Actor\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that David Burtka is a multi-talented actor, and there are multiple instances across different files (63.txt, 105.txt, 96.txt) where his acting career is highlighted. Therefore, based on this context information, it can be concluded that David Burtka was indeed an Actor."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that David Burtka is a multi-talented actor, involved in various acting roles and performances. Therefore, the triple \"David Burtka was an Actor\" is correct according to the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "David Burtka is not just an actor; he is a man of many talents, including being a chef, a singer, a host, and a magician. This indicates that his primary profession is not solely acting.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state he is an actor, listing his roles and work.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information consistently describes David Burtka as a multi-talented individual, listing his skills as an actor, chef, singer, host, magician, and more, indicating that acting is just one of many talents he possesses.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information consistently portrays David Burtka as a multi-talented individual with an acting career, but does not provide any evidence suggesting he was never an actor. On the contrary, his acting roles and fame are highlighted throughout the provided details.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}